University Advancement fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
University Advancement fonds
1958 - 2015
F-53
1.27 m of textual records 3 photographs
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Office name changes include: Resources Office (1966 - 1982) Development Office (1982 - 1998) University Advancement (2000 - ) PHYSICAL DESCRIPTION: 3 photographs located in F-53-1-2-0-22
University Advancement
The Office of University Advancement is responsible for fund raising initiatives to support the university's teaching, research, and service objectives.
Organized fund raising activities began at SFU in 1966, when the Resources Office was established. This office was responsible for following up pledges to the Three Universities Capital Fund, which had been established in 1963. The Resources Office was also responsible for establishing and developing new, permanent fund raising programs. Originally, the Resources Office reported directly to the University President. In 1971, the office of Vice-President, Development (later renamed Vice-President, University Services) was created, which then took on responsibility for the Resources Office. In 1977, the position of Vice-President, University Services was eliminated, and the Resources Office again reported directly to the President.
In 1982 the Resources Office was renamed Development Office and reported to the newly-created Vice-President, University Development and Extension. In 1988, the Director of Development began reporting to the Vice-President, Harbour Centre. In 2000 the office was renamed University Advancement.
The Office of University Advancement has close ties with the SFU Alumni Association, which was founded by SFU graduates in 1969, and which provides programs and services to assist SFU and its graduates. The Association is a registered nonprofit society governed by an elected board of volunteers. The Alumni Relations Office provides administrative support for all Association activities. It also publishes the Alumni Journal, maintains alumni records, and serves as the main point of contact for alumni on the SFU campus. From 1971 to 1972, this office reported to the Director of Resources. From 1973 to 1975, the office reported directly to the Vice-President, University Services, but still maintained close ties to the Resources Office. From 1977 to 1984, the office was again made a responsibility of the Director of Resources (also referred to as the Director of Development). By 1986, the Alumni Relations Office reported directly to the Vice-President, University Development and Extension, but was still linked to the Development Office. In 1988, the Director of Alumni Relations began reporting to the Vice-President, Harbour Centre.
published
Full
Revised
The title is based on the name of the creating body.
Fonds consists of records arising from the activities of the SFU Development Office and its predecessors, records of the SFU Alumni Association, and records from the Three Universities Capital Fund. Fonds includes correspondence, memoranda, reports, promotional materials, address lists, lists of donations, newsletters, photographs, and other materials.
Daminato, Cathy; Gill, Warren; Godin, Victor; Edgar, Dvorka; Clarke, Margaret; Nelson, Madeleine; Bean, Bill; Leach, Joy B.; Klassen, William; McRae, Ted; Hendy, Martin; Palmer, Wilford; Willett, Sandy; Wooley, M.; Hefelfinger, Jane; Photographic materials; Textual records
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed (as of February 2006: 73 cm., 1966-1983). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
Series descriptions, subseries descriptions, and file lists are available.
- Director of Development, 1966 - 2002; F-53-1; 55 cm of textual records 3 photographs; Physical description: 3 photographs located in F-53-1-2-0-22
  published
  Series consists of records arising from the activities of the Director of Development. Series includes correspondence, memoranda, reports, manuals, promotional literature, photographs, and other materials.
  - Correspondence, 1966 - 1975; F-53-1-1; 37 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of correspondence of the Director of Development. Subseries includes copies of outgoing correspondence and memoranda. Correspondents include university officials, donors, charitable foundations, and other organizations.
    Access to some records in series may be restricted, in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Please consult the unit list and the archivist for details.
    - Chronological correspondence, 1966; F-53-1-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
      Textual records
      Pending review
    - Chronological correspondence, 1967; F-53-1-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1967; F-53-1-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1967; F-53-1-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-53-1-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-53-1-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-53-1-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-53-1-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-53-1-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-53-1-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-53-1-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-53-1-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-53-1-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-53-1-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-53-1-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-53-1-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-53-1-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 53-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-53-1-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-53-1-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-53-1-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-53-1-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-53-1-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-53-1-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-53-1-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-53-1-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-53-1-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-53-1-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-53-1-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-53-1-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - [Empty], F-53-1-1-0-31
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-53-1-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-53-1-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-53-1-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-53-1-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-53-1-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-53-1-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-53-1-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-53-1-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-53-1-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-53-1-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-53-1-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-53-1-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-53-1-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-53-1-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-53-1-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-53-1-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-53-1-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-53-1-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-53-1-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 53-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-53-1-1-0-120 (Archival box - standard 53-2)
  - Reports and promotional literature, 1968 - 2002; F-53-1-2; 17 cm of textual records 3 photographs
    Subseries consists of reports, manuals, reviews, promotional literature, and other materials of the Director of Development. Subseries also includes some correspondence and memoranda. Materials relate to fund raising, foundations, the performance of the Development Office, and other matters.
    - Foundations Manual, 1972 - 1986; F-53-1-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Resources office - Miscellaneous 10th Anniversary Fund, Vice-Pres. File, 1973; F-53-1-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Misc. Corres. and Memos, Vice-Pres. file, 1973; F-53-1-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Resources Report, Vice-Pres. file, 1972; F-53-1-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Miscellaneous Chronological correspondence and Memoaranda, 1974; F-53-1-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Miscellaneous Chronological correspondence and Memoaranda, 1974; F-53-1-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Donation Report Procedures, 1974; F-53-1-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Misc. re CP Air Travel Assistance Program, 1977; F-53-1-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Certificate of Presentation Case (samples) given donors of Permanent Endowments, 1968; F-53-1-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - A Review of Ceremonies Administration at Six Canadian Universities, 1979; F-53-1-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Tenth Anniversary Fund Promotional Literature, 1975; F-53-1-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
      Open
    - Organization of scholarships, bursaries, and awards, 1970 - 1971; F-53-1-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Resume of Activities of Resources Officer, A Report, 1969; F-53-1-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Resources Office Report to External Affairs Committee, 1969; F-53-1-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Revision of Report Submitted April 2, 1970, F-53-1-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - A Preliminary Approach to an Integrated Funding Program For SFU, 1970; F-53-1-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Request for BOG Approach of Proposed Solicitation Campaign, 1970; F-53-1-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Report on Fund-Raising, 1974; F-53-1-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Comments on 10th Anniversary Fund, 1974; F-53-1-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - A Report on the Resources Office at SFU by S.Segal, 1975; F-53-1-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Report of the Resources Office, 1976; F-53-1-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 53-4)
    - Staff photographs, 1998 - 2002; F-53-1-2-0-22
      Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Staff photo jig-saw puzzle, 1998; F-53-1-2-0-23
    - Simon Fraser University Fieldhouse Report, April 1989; F-53-1-2-0-24
    - Simon Fraser University Fieldhouse Report, May 1989; F-53-1-2-0-25
    - SFU at Harbour Centre proposed floor plans, January 1988; F-53-1-2-0-26
- General fundraising, 1967 - 1979; F-53-2; 13 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records arising from the administration of ongoing fund raising activities of the Development office, including annual fund drives. Series includes correspondence, memoranda, reports, promotional literature, and other materials.
  - Annual Fund Drive, 1967; F-53-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Annual Fund Drive, 1968; F-53-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Annual Fund Drive, 1976; F-53-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Annual Fund Drive - a proposal for the 1977 annual drive, F-53-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Annual Fund Drive, 1978; F-53-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Annual Fund Drive, 1979; F-53-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Fund raising, Vice-President's File, 1973; F-53-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Tenth Anniversary Fund, Vice-President's File, 1973; F-53-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Reports and memos re fund raising, Vice-Pres. unsorted file, 1973; F-53-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Reports and memos re fund raising, Vice-Pres. unsorted file, 1973; F-53-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Reports and memos re fund raising, Vice-Pres. unsorted file, 1973; F-53-2-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Misellaneous reports, V.P.'s file, 1974 - 1975; F-53-2-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Resources - general, V.P.'s file (letters to donors), 1975; F-53-2-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Resources - general, V.P.'s file (letters to donors), 1973 - 1975; F-53-2-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Miscellaneous re donations received (letters to donors), 1975; F-53-2-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Correspondence re Friends of Simon, 1976; F-53-2-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Miscellaneous Memos and corres., V.P.s file, 1975; F-53-2-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Misellaneous correspondence and proposals from Fund Raising Agencies, 1974 - 1975; F-53-2-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Personnel - Resources office, 1975 - 1976; F-53-2-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
  - Resources office - administration, 1977; F-53-2-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 53-5)
- Three Universities Capital Fund, 1958 - 1980; F-53-3; 31 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records arising from the administration of the Three Universities Capital Fund campaign. Series includes correspondence, address lists, lists of donations and refusals, promotional material, and other items.
  - Correspondence, 1964 - 1969; F-53-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Publications, 1964 - 1969; F-53-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - SFU Invitation List, 1965; F-53-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Potential Leadership Master List, 1964; F-53-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Master List Suggested Targets, 1964; F-53-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Correspondence - General (includes pledge cancellations), 1966 - 1969; F-53-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Preliminary List of Major Gifts Possible Donors, 1964; F-53-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Auditor's Report, 1968; F-53-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Progress Reports (incomplete series), 1967 - 1969; F-53-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Correspondence - Co-Chairmen (lists of donations, 1966 - 1970; F-53-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Prospect Assignment Sheets, F-53-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Employee Solicitation Handbook, 1965; F-53-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Guides for Personal Gifts, F-53-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Executive Gift Division, 1964 - 1965; F-53-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Professional Division (lists of donations and refusals), 1965; F-53-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Building Contracts for the Three Universities, 1966 - 1969; F-53-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Correspondence - B.C. Hydro, 1966; F-53-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Major Gift Prospects Outside B.C., 1964; F-53-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Major Gifts - Head Office B.C., 1964; F-53-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Report of Returns (incomplete) - list of donations, 1966 - 1967; F-53-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Specimen Letters, 1965 - 1966; F-53-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Master List - Burnaby - Lower Fraser Valley (with comments as to donations and refusals, 1965; F-53-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Drop List, 1967; F-53-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 53-6)
  - Organization Chart for Fund Drive, 1965; F-53-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Publicity Pamphlets and Brochures, 1958 - 1965; F-53-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Publicity Pamphlets and Brochures, 1963 - 1966; F-53-3-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Reports of Resources/BOG Confidential Meeting, 1970; F-53-3-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Complete Listing of all Gift, 1968; F-53-3-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Complete Listing of all Gift, 1966 - 1968; F-53-3-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Presentation Brochure for Capital Fund, F-53-3-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Advance Personal List (with comments as to donations and refusals, 1965; F-53-3-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Prospect - Duplication Sheet (lists of donations), 1966; F-53-3-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - SFU Building Fund Draft Invitation List, 1964; F-53-3-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - SFU Convocation Founders Addenda, 1964; F-53-3-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Wills and Bequests - Brochures and Promotional Literature, F-53-3-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Copy of Agreement to Establish Three Univ. Capital Fund, 1964; F-53-3-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 53-7)
  - Propositions re SFU Fund Raising During Post 3 Univ. Capital Fund Period, 1968; F-53-3-0-0-37 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Professional Fund Raisers, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1968 - 1969; F-53-3-0-0-38 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Treasury - Pledge Payments Received, 1966; F-53-3-0-0-39 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Report on Corporate Aid to Higher Education (AUCC), 1967; F-53-3-0-0-40 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Treasury - Designated Gifts, 1966; F-53-3-0-0-41 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Summary Report of Returns, 1966; F-53-3-0-0-42 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Fund Payments Received, 1966; F-53-3-0-0-43 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Briefs of Canadian Universities Foundation, 1963; F-53-3-0-0-44 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - President's (McTaggart-Cowan) Files, 1964; F-53-3-0-0-45 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - President's (McTaggart-Cowan) Files, 1964; F-53-3-0-0-46 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Capital Funds Goals, 1964 - 1969; F-53-3-0-0-47 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Correspondence, 1966 - 1968; F-53-3-0-0-48 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Financial Statement, 1979 - 1980; F-53-3-0-0-49 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Advance Personal Prespective, 1965; F-53-3-0-0-50 (Archival box - small 53-8)
  - Residual Prospects, 1966; F-53-3-0-0-51 (Archival box - small 53-8)
- Alumni Relations Office, 1968 - 2015; F-53-4; 32 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records produced by the SFU Alumni Relations Office, in support of the Alumni Association. Series includes the association constitution, minutes, correspondence and memoranda, brochures and other promotional material, and copies of alumni newsletters entitled The Bridge, Afterthoughts, the Alumni Journal, and AQ magazine.
  - Constitution, 1968 - 1989; F-53-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Minutes of Executive, 1971; F-53-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
    Restricted in part
  - Vice-President's file, 1973; F-53-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Misc. Alumni Association, V.P.s file, 1975; F-53-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Events, 1986; F-53-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - The Bridge, Vol. 1 (Bridge to the Future), 1988; F-53-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Silver Anniversary watch promotional material, 1990; F-53-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Annual Reports, 1985 - 2007; F-53-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Travel Study promotional materials, 1993; F-53-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Brochures, 1986 - 1989; F-53-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - The Bridge, Vol. 1, 1969; F-53-4-0-0-11 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - The Bridge, Vol. 2, 1969 - 1970; F-53-4-0-0-12 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - The Bridge, Vol. 3, no. 1-6, 1970 - 1971; F-53-4-0-0-13 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - The Bridge, Vol. 3, no. 7-12, [ca 1972] - [ca 1973]; F-53-4-0-0-14 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - Afterthoughts, Vol. 1, 1973 - 1974; F-53-4-0-0-15 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - Afterthoughts, Vol. 2, 1974 - 1975; F-53-4-0-0-16 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - Afterthoughts, Vol. 3, 1975 - 1976; F-53-4-0-0-17 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - Afterthoughts, Vol. 4, 1976 - 1977; F-53-4-0-0-18 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - Afterthoughts, Vol. 5, 1977 - 1978; F-53-4-0-0-19 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - Afterthoughts, Vol. 6, 1978 - 1979; F-53-4-0-0-20 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - Afterthoughts, Vol. 7, 1977 - 1980; F-53-4-0-0-21 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - Afterthoughts, Vol. 8, 1980 - 1981; F-53-4-0-0-22 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - Afterthoughts, Vol. 9, 1981 - 1982; F-53-4-0-0-23 (Newspaper box 53-11)
  - [Empty], F-53-4-0-0-24
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 1, 1983; F-53-4-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 2, 1984; F-53-4-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 3, 1985; F-53-4-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 4, 1986; F-53-4-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 5, 1987; F-53-4-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 6, 1988; F-53-4-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 7, 1989; F-53-4-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 8, 1990; F-53-4-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 53-9)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 9, 1991; F-53-4-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 10, 1992; F-53-4-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 11, 1993; F-53-4-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 12, 1994; F-53-4-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 13, 1995; F-53-4-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 14, 1996; F-53-4-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 15, 1997; F-53-4-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 16, 1998; F-53-4-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - Alumni Journal, Vol. 17, 1999; F-53-4-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - AQ, Vol. 1, 2000; F-53-4-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - AQ, Vol. 2, 2001; F-53-4-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - AQ, Vol. 3, 2002; F-53-4-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - AQ, Vol. 4, 2003; F-53-4-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - AQ, Vol. 5, 2004; F-53-4-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - AQ, Vol. 6, 2005; F-53-4-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - AQ, Vol. 7, 2006; F-53-4-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 53-10)